Guide to the John H. Whitlock papers, 1937-1977,
Whitlock, John H. papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John H. Whitlock papers, 1937-1977, 1968-1977 (bulk).
24-2-2203
Whitlock, John H.,
11.7 cubic ft.
Correspondence, minutes, financial records, photographs and mimeographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Personal correspondence; correspondence, minutes, and bills relating to the University Senate and Constituent Assembly and the University Faculty; mimeographed Faculty and Senate records; and Board of Trustees correspondence and mimeographs; also professional correspondence and work, and photographs.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of veterinary preventive medicine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Personal correspondence; correspondence, minutes, and bills relating to the University Senate and Constituent Assembly and the University Faculty; mimeographed Faculty and Senate records; and Board of Trustees correspondence and mimeographs; also professional correspondence and work, and photographs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Whitlock, John H., 1913-; Cornell University -- Faculty.; Cornell University; Cornell University. Senate.; Cornell University. Board of Trustees.; Cornell University. Board of Trustees; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.
Subjects:
Universities and colleges -- Faculty
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. C.U. Board of Trustees Meetings and Business
Series III. Faculty Council Representatives
Series IV. University Faculty
Series V. Board of Trustees
Series VI. Board of Trustees Financial (Budgets)
Series VII. Cornell University Senate
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1938-1976
  Personal correspondence in Box 1 is restricted to permission of donor.
  - Office Files: Correspondence, memorandum and corresponding IBM magnetic cards, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - J. H. Whitlock, Ancient Correspondence, also a copy of Practical Identification of Endoparasites for veterinarians, by J. H. Whitlock, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1956-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Air Rights Proposal Letters, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Norman Baker Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Blood... The Journal of Hematology", 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Samuel H. Boyer, M.D., correspondence, The John Hopkins Hospital, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - A. J. E. Bucknor correspondence (Ghanna), 1964-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - R. V. Brunsdon letter, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - D. C. Burgett correspondence, college registrar, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Patricia Carry correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Center for Study of Democratic Institutions, Santa Barbara, California, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - C.I.S. - Center for International Studies, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Center for Environmental Quality Management, 1966-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Center for Environmental Quality Management, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Law Review, Robert Levine (ed-in-chief), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Article; "Computing in Medicine", 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Richard Clark, correspondence, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Change related material, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Constituent Assembly materials (proposals, news articles, letters, amendments, memos), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Harry Crofton correspondence and papers, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Harry Crofton correspondence and papers, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Harry Crofton insurance, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Curriculum revision - Kansas State, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - C.S.I.R.O. letter, and paper on "Stocking Intensity and Nematode Infection of Grazing Sheep", 1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - K. G. Davey correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - A. D. Donald correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - D. Sc. Degree - graduate faculty, Veterinary Medicine, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - J. D. Dunsmore - Division Wildlife Research - Australia, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - S. A. Ewing, Kansas State U. (Dept. of Path.), 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Paul Feeney correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - John P. Dessaver, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - G. E. Ford, U. of Melbourne, 1965-1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Ford Foundation Training Grant, 1965-1972 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Geigy Agricultural Chemicals, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Kay Hanna, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - C. R. Henderson, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Burton Hermann, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Donald Heyneman, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Lap True Huynn, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - John Junt, U. of Hawaii, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Harry Hoogstraal correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Donald Kagan, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Robert Kane, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Keith Kennedy (vice-provost), 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Prof. J. Kingsbury, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Richard Korf, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - John Kramer and Ed Smith, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Lea and Febiger, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - William Lower, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - F. A. Long, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Thomas Mackesey, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - H. Madsen, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Master Plan Discussion, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - H. McCredie, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - J. F. Michel, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - R. C. Mosteller (Paper), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - R. S. Morison, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - R. P. Murphy, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Paul Olum, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - James A. Perkins, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Howard E. Quirk, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - T. R. Rogers, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Robert F. Risley, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Clark Read, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Ratner Report, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Planning Board and Bd. of Supervisors, Town of Dryden, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Alan Sapakie, Asst. Ombudsman, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Fred M. Saperston, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Scientific Research, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - W. H. Southcott, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - R. W. Sutherst, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Reports of Presidential Commission of Military Training and Selective Service, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Papers Dealing With Cornell's Issues of Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - R. J. Thomas, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Jack D. Tiner, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Lincicome: "Effects of Heat and Iodine on Eldysis of Infective Haemonchus Contortus Cayugensis Larvae", 1969 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Paul Van Riper, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Vet Faculty, General - also a report of the Committee to Study the Problems of Veterinary Medical Education, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Graduate College (and Faculty) of Veterinary Medicine, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Vet College - General Committee, 1958-1975 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Robin Williams - Faculty Review, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Women's Caucus, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - W. D. Youngs, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Veterinary Students - Foreign Schools, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Curriculum Vitae of Whitlock, Undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
- C.U. Board of Trustees Meetings and Business, 1969-1976
  - Commencement Committee, Cornell Fund Report, 1976-05-28 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Agenda, 1976-05-27 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Supplemental Agenda, 1976-05-27 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Tenure Decisions and Affirmative Action Proposals, 1976-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Agenda - Executive Committeemen, 1976-05-11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memo on Commencement Meeting, 1976-05-13 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Memo on B.O.T. Nominations and Elections, 1976-04-27 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Memo on Commencement Meeting, 1976-04-27 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Agenda, Minutes, Supplemental Agenda, 1976-03-19-1976-03-20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Agenda; Supplemental Agenda; Minutes; Cornell Fund Report, 1976-03-18 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Minority Report on the Committee to Establish a Commission to Study Self-Government, 1976-03-12 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1976-03-09 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Article from New York Times on KY Episode; Report on KY Episode (Dec. 9, 1975), 1976-03-07 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Letter to B.O.T. from David Knapp, 1976-03-03 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1976-02-19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Proposal for Cornell to Fulfill Its Public Service Mandate to N.Y. State, 1976-02-02 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Minutes; Remarks to B.O.T. from R.S. Morison; Cornell Fund Report; Agenda, 1976-01-30-1976-01-31 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1976-01-29 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Memo/Report from Henry Paley to Executive Officers and CICU Institutions, 1976-01-23 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Memo for the Record, J.R. Barlow, 1976-01-21 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1976-01-12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1976-01-02 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The N.Y. State Master Plan - 1976, of Cornell University, 1976-01 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Committee, 1975-12-09 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Report of the AD HOC Committee on Capital Financing and Financial Planning, 1975-12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1975-11-11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Memo to B.O.T. (not on Ex. Comm.), 1975-10-17 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Agenda; Minutes; Memo; Cornell Fund Report; Report Listing from Ex. Committee, 1975-10-10-1975-10-11 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1975-10-09 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Analysis re: Debt, 1975-09-30 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1975-09-29 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Minority Report of the Trustee AD HOC Comm. on Athletics (J.T. Younger), 1975-09-21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Report of the AD HOC (Trustee) Comm. on Athletics, 1975-09-21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1975-09-11-1975-09-12 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1975-09-09 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1975-08-28 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1975-08-20 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1975-07-22 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Memo to Executive Committee, 1975-07-14 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Agenda; Minutes; Supplemental Agenda, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Agenda; Minutes; Supplemental Agenda; Election of Presidential Councillors; Guest List from Stamp Cocktail Reception; B.O.T. Agenda for May 31-June 3, 1975, 1975-05-31-1975-06-03 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Fund Report, 1975-05-30 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Invitation to B.O.T., 1975-05-27 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1975-05-14 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Memo to B.O.T., Ex. Comm. (D.R. Corson), 1975-05-13 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1975-05-06 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Report to B.O.T. (Provost Knapp), 1975-05 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Memo to B.O.T. not on Ex. Committee, 1975-04-10 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Committee, 1975-04-08 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Letter to M. Adams from J.J.Meng, 1975-04-03 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Letter to M. Adams from J.C.C. Edelstein, 1975-03-30 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Letter to Meng, Edelstein, and Toll from M. Adams, 1975-03-26 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Agenda and Minutes, 1975-03-14-1975-03-15 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, Cornell, Presentation to B.O.T.; Agenda; Minutes; Supplemental Adenda, 1975-03-13 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Letter to E. L. Boyer from Dale R. Corson, 1975-02-27 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1975-02-11 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Agenda and Minutes, 1975-01-17-1975-01-18 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Agenda; Minutes; Supplemental Agenda, 1975-01-16 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate Student Activities Funds; 1974-75 Budger and Special Projects Allocations, 1975-01-15 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - B.O.T. Schedule of Activities, 1975-01-15-1975-01-18 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1974-12-10 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1974-11-12 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Tentative Schedule of Activities, B.O.T., 1974-10-10-1974-10-12 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Agenda; Minutes; Supplemental Agenda, 1974-10-11-1974-10-12 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Charts Relating to the Development Advisory Committee Report, 1974-10-12 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1974-10-10 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1974-09-10 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - B.O.T., Buildings and Properties Comm., 1974-09-09 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Minutes of the Joint Administrative Board, 1974-09-04 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Agenda and Minutes, Ex. Comm., 1974-07-18 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Agenda and Supplemental Agenda, 1974-06-02 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Agenda and Supplemental Agenda, 1974-06-01 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Fund Report, 1974-05-31 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Report on Long-Term Student Housing Needs, 1974-05-30 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Memo to R.M. Ramin from Randall E. Shew, 1974-05-28 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Student Apartment Project, Cost and Rental Income, 1974-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Apartment Project - Income/Expense Projection, 1974-05-21 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1974-05-14 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1974-05-08 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1974-04-17 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Agenda, 1974-03-15-1974-03-16 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Agenda and Supplemental Agenda, 1974-03-14 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1974-02-12 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Agenda, 1974-01-18-1974-01-19 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1974-01-17 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Memo to B.O.T., Academic Tenure, 1974-01-14 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Press Release, to Council on Federal Relations, Citizens' Commission of Private Philanthropy and Public Needs, 1973-11-20 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1973-12-11 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1973-11-15 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agenda and Schedule of Activities, 1973-10-18-1973-10-20 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1973-10-18 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1973-10-10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Memo to B.O.T., 1973-09-24 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Agenda, Ex. Committee, 1973-09-11 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Agenda, Ex. Committee, 1973-07-19 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Schedule of Events, B.O.T., 1973-05-22-1973-05-25 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Commencement, 1973-05-25 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Agenda and Supplemental Agenda, 1973-05-24 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Agenda and Supplemental Agenda, 1973-05-23 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1973-04-18 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Memo to B.O.T. not on Ex. Comm., 1973-04-11 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Agenda, 1973-03-16-1973-03-17 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1973-03-15 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Agenda and Supplemental Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1973-02-21 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Agenda, 1973-01-26-1973-01-27 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Agenda, Ex. Committee, 1973-01-25 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Agenda, Ex. Committee, 1972-12-20 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1972-11-15 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Agenda and Supplemental Agenda, 1972-10-13-1972-10-14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1972-09-20 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1972-07-12 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Agenda, 1972-05-25 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Agenda and Supplementals, 1972-05-24 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1972-04-12 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Agenda, 1972-03-17-1972-03-18 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1972-03-16 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Minutes of the Joint Administrative Board, 1972-03-15 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1972-02-16 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1972-01-21-1972-01-22 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Agenda, 1972-01-20 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1971-12-15 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1971-11-17 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Schedule of Events (Trustee-Council Weekend), 1971-10-14-1971-10-17 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Agenda, 1971-10-15-1971-10-16 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1971-10-14 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1971-09-08 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Agenda, 1971-07-21 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Agenda, Ex. Comm., 1971-07-21 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Minutes, B.O.T., 1971-07-01 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Minutes of Joint Administrative Board, 1971-06-16 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Cornell By Laws, 1969-01-1975-06 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Amended Cornell Charter, 1969-07-1975-08 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - B.O.T. Buildings and Properties Committee, 1972-02-1974-08 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - B.O.T. Carpenter Hall Decision - Text, 1972-05-24 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Comm. to Study Feasibility of C.U. in Health Prof. Educ., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - B.O.T. Cornell Medical Center (N.Y. Hospital), 1972-12 (Box 3, Folder 30-32)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971-10-1975-01 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Committee of Cornell-State Relations, 1972-03-1976-07 (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
- Faculty Council Representatives, 1950-1976
  - F. C.R. Appointment Procedures (Faculty), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - F.C.R. Effort Allocation, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - F.C.R. Hare System, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - F.C.R. General, 1968-1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - F.C.R. Memos and Agendas, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Minutes of F.C.R., 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Minutes of F.C.R., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of F.C.R., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of F.C.R., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of F.C.R., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Robert McKersie - Racism Situation, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - F.C.R. Members, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - F.C.R. Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - F.C.R. Committee on Academic Freedom and Responsibility, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - F.C.R. Committee on Academic Programs and Policies, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - F.C.R. Committee of Academic Integrity Hearing and Appeals, 1969-1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - F.C.R. Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on Academic Records and Instruction, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on Calendar and Schedules, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on Freedom of Academic Teaching and Learning, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on Military Training, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on Minority Education, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on Nominations and Elections, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on Physical Education, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on the Professional and Economic Status of the Faculty, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on R.O.T.C. Relationships, 1960-1974 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on R.O.T.C. Relationships, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - F.C.R. Committee on Rules and Procedures for Governing Standing Comm., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - F.C.R. Comm. to Establish a Commission to Study Self-Governance, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - F.C.R. Comm. on University Research Policies, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - F.C.R. Executive Committee - General, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - F.C.R. Ex. Comm. Memos to Members - Notice of Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - F.C.R. Ex. Comm. Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - F.C.R. Ex. Comm. Agendas and Memos; F.C.R. Interim Ex. Comm. Minutes, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - F.C.R. Interim Ex. Comm. - General, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - F.C.R. Committee Member Rosters, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - R. Miller - Former Dean of Faculty, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Ombudsman, Alice Cook, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Norman Penney, Dean of Faculty, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Norman Penney, Dean of Faculty, 1950-1973 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Publications; Inform. Reports, etc., 1950-1973 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, Minutes and Memos - F.C.R., 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- University Faculty, 1965-1976
  - Agendas and Meeting Notices, 1968-1976 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Calspan Corp. Relations - CAL, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - COSEP - Comm. on Special Educational Projects, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - COSEP, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Comm. on Membership of U.F., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Comm. on Nominations and Elections, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Dept. Economics - McPhelin Charges, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - U.F. General, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - U.F. Comm. on Independent Courses, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - U.F. Meetings (Agendas, Memos ... ), 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - U.F. Membership, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - U.F. Memorial Statements, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Minutes, 1968-1976 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Comm. on Organization and Procedures, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Common Research Grants, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Orientation Program, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Pasley Report, etc., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Policy Notebook for Students and Grading at Cornell, 1963-1971 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Review and Procedures CorrIDittee, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Faculty Legislation - Resolutions and Correcting, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Student Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Student Affairs, 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Student Affairs, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Student Affairs, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Student Affairs, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Board of Trustees, 1970-1976
  - Councils, Colleges and Schools - Reports, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School of Medical Sciences, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Dialogue" (The Tower Club), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - B.O.T. General, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - B.O.T. General, 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Marcus Brothers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Master Plans, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Master Plans, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Members, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Minorities, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Report of Trustee Ad Hoc Comm. on Status of Minorities, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Photographic Policy, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Regents Report, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 13-14)
  - David Safadi, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - John L. Senior - Chair, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Neal Stamp - Sec. of Univ. Council, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Status of Women, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Trustee - Community Communications, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Trustee - Planning committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tuition Contracts, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - B.O.T. Vacancies and Nominations, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Board of Trustees Financial (Budgets)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Memos and Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Memos; Budget; Letters, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Budget - supporting data and narrative, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Budget - endowed colleges, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Budget - endowed units, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Overall Budget Plan, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Fund Campaign, 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Cornell University Gift Report, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Financing Higher Education, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Fiscal Information, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Fiscal Information, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 34-35)
  - Fiscal Information, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - B.O.T. Executive Committee Financial Information, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - B.O.T. and Ex. Committee Financial Information, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - B.O.T. and Ex. Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Ex Committee Fiscal Information, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Fiscal Information - Ex. Comm., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 41)